昨晚发生了叛乱 两名士兵受伤
There was a revolt last night and two soldiers were wounded.
说吧
Tell me,
你们觉得我会对你们怎么样
what do you think I should do with you?
根据法律我可以绞死你们 但是我想
The law authorizes me to hang you, but I wonder...
这对我有什么好处
What good would that do?
我知道你们把我们当做敌人
I know you see us as the enemy.
觉得我们从你们手里抢走了土地
You think we snatched your land away from you.
你们错了
You're wrong!
我要你们给佐罗送个信
I want one of you to take this message to Zorro.
牵马来
A horsel
杀了他
Kill him.
背后偷袭
In the back?
开枪 不然我就开枪了
Shoot, or I will.
开枪
Shoot.
下次你要违抗我的命令
The next time you disobey an order,
我就一枪崩了你 上尉
I'll have you shot, Captain
看到了吗
Do you see?
这不是很好吗
Isn't it good?
我们刚刚除掉了这个团伙的头目
We just eliminated the ringleader of this group.
现在我们等待法官
Now we wait for the judge...
然后处决你们
and then you'll be executed.
报告中写 企图逃跑
Put in the report: "attempted escape".
我连他名字都不知道
I don't even know his name.
这重要吗
What does that matter?
没有法官回来的
No judge will be coming.
把他们埋在郊外
And bury them outside the cemetery.
他们是畜生
They re animals.
不配在神圣的地下长眠
They don't deserve to rest in hallowed ground.
牵我的马
My horse!
他叫什么名字
What was his name?
你好像对你哥哥的死不太悲伤
You don't seem very sad about the death of your brother.
我哥是个大混蛋
My brother was a real son of a bitch.
幸运的是 他意外去世了
Fortunately, he died unexpectedly,
不然的话 他肯定会剥夺我的继承权
otherwise...he would've surely disinherited me.
好像他们抓住了佐罗的人
It seems they've captured Zorro's men.
信上这么说的
The letter said so.
就算是 我也不信
Even so, I don't trust it.
洛杉矶变得极度危险
Los Angeles is becoming a very dangerous place.
所以你才雇了我
That's why you hired me.
不必担心
You needn't worry.
怎么了
What's wrong?
路上有个死掉的女人
There's a dead woman on the road.
好像是个农场主
She looks like a rancher.
去扶她上车
Get her,
不过放在后面
but put her in back,
我可不想被她熏臭
I don't want her stinking us out.
快点
Quickly!
去帮他
Go with him.
别激动
Relax.
别激动 别激动
Relax. Relax.
如果你还想活着看到拉米雷斯的弟弟 就放了我的人
IF YOU WANT TO SEE RAMIREZ'S BROTHER ALIVE AGAIN, FREE MY MEN.
没有他的踪影
No trace of him.
没有 长官
No, sir.
你认为他是说真的吗
Do you think he means it?
马车夫和保镖都死了
The coachman and the gunman were dead.
记住 现在有两个了
Remember, there are two now.
你百分百确定吗 上尉
Are you completely sure of this, Captain?
完全确定 我亲眼所见
Absolutely, I saw it with my own eyes.
两个佐罗
Two Zorros.
这不合理
It makes no sense.
可能是他和他的徒弟
Perhaps he is his pupil.
一个已经够我们应付的了
As if we didn't have enough with one.
好好调查一下
Look into it.
我查过了 好像没人知情
I did, but no one seems to know anything.
这件事我不需要外传 一个字都不能传出去
I don't want a word of this to get out, to anyone.
只有一个佐罗 他没有帮手
There's only one Zorro and he's alone.
我说清楚了吗
Is that clear?
是 长官
Yes, sir.
找到拉米雷斯的弟弟
Find Ramirez's brother.
这事公开了吗
Is it public?
还没有
Not yet.
What are you going to do about it? 你打算怎么做
加利福尼亚充满机遇 记住了
California is the land of opportunities, remember.
当然
Of course.
回答你的问题 安德列耶维奇先生 取决于
The answer to your question, Mr. Andreyevich, depends.
俄美公司为收购拉米雷斯煤矿
On the price the Russo- American Company is willing to pay
愿意支付的价格
to acquire Ramirez's coal mine.
当然前提是要出售
Were it available, of course.
假如拉米雷斯兄弟死亡 会出售吗
Would it be available if Ramirez's brother dies?
他们没有继承人 财产会移交给政府
There are no more heirs. It'd pass to the government.
墨西哥为何还想要一座矿
Why does Mexico want another mine?
价钱不是问题
The price won't be a problem.
我很高兴听到这么说
I'm glad to hear it.
正义 正X
Justicel Justicel
下一枪就致命了
The next one will kill!
马上散开
Disperse!
怎么回事 上尉
What's going on, Captain?
不用担心
You needn't worry about anything.
你都开枪了还说没事
You shoot people for nothing?
我的任务是保证安全 德拉维加先生
My mission is to ensure peace, Mr. De la Vega.
我不准再发生任何争吵
I won't allow any more altercations.
你实在要知道的话 佐罗绑架了拉米雷斯的弟弟
And if you want to know, Zorro abducted Ramirez's brother.
他想让州长释放他的人来做交换
Now he wants the Governor to free his people in exchange for him.
州长绝对不会同意的
The Governor will never allow that.
事实上 他已经下令三天后处决他们
In fact, he's ordered them to be executed in three days.
不经过审判吗
Without a trial?
以儆效尤
Exemplary measures.
你的看法呢
And what's your opinion?
我没看法 我只听从命令
I have no opinion, I follow orders.
我建议你小心点 迪亚哥 现在可不是农场主的好时代
I advise you to be careful, Diego. These aren't good times for ranchers.
失陪
If I may
我来传个口信
I've come to give you a message.
我们都知道娜·琳做了什么
We all know what Nah- Lin has done.
有些人认为很公平
Some of you think it is fair.
但是我向你们保证 这只会带来死亡和毁灭
But I can assure you that this path only brings death and destruction.
看看你们周围
Look around you.
因为她的行为你们已经失去了家园
You've lost your homes because of her actions.
复仇是讨不回公道的
There is no justice in revenge.
只会带来痛苦
Only pain.
你们想这样吗
Is that what you want?
或许拉米雷斯是该死
Maybe Ramirez deserved to die,
可他弟弟是无辜的
but his brother is innocent.
你们想给州长罔顾法律
Do you want to give the Governor an excuse
随意杀人的理由吗
to kill at his whim and disregard the law?
杀了雷米拉斯的弟弟
Kill Ramirez's brother,
不过别算在我头上
but don't count on me.
佐罗不杀无辜之人 我要娜·琳知道这一点
Zorro does not kill the innocent. I need Nah- Lin to know this.
你杀了我 你的人就会死
If you kill me, your men will die.
而报复 想象一下会怎么样吧
And the reprisals...Imagine what will happen,
我不相信富人的公正
I don't believe in the justice of the rich.
我也不信
Nor do I.
但是如果拉米雷斯的弟弟三天之内不出现
But if Ramirez's brother doesn't appear in three days,
你的人必死无疑
your men will not survive.
放了他 你的人还有一线生机
Free him and they'll have a chance to survive.
上尉 你抓住了罪犯 干的真漂亮
Captain, you've done a fine job with those criminals.
法律高于一切 我们全都要遵守
The law is above everyone and it must be complied with.
无一例外
Without exceptions.
佐罗呢 你有他的线索吗
And Zorro? Do you have a lead on him?
我估计他走投无路了
I think he's desperate.
我们抓了他的同伙 下一个就是他
We captured his collaborators. He'll be next full stop
到时候我们再庆祝
And we will celebrate it accordingly.
在那之前 我们不能放松警惕
Until then, we cannot let our guard down.
最近发生了这么多事 必须提高警惕
With what's happening lately, it's only natural.
加利福尼亚已经变得非常疯狂
California is becoming a very wild land.
-现在进城安全吗  -你是说因为有佐罗吗
- Is it safe to go to town now? - Do you mean because of Zorro?
还有城里的抗议
Also, but because of the protests.
这些叛乱企图必须镇压
These attempts at rebellion must be suppressed.
不然就像野火一样蔓延 露西娅夫人
Or they'd spread like wildfire, Dofia Lucia.
但这种严厉会不会反过来对你不利呢
But cannot such severity end up turning against you?
维持秩序是头等大事
The main thing is to keep order.
与佐罗谈判将使他合法化
Negotiating with Zorro would legitimize him,
因此 我们的选择不多
so, unfortunately, we don't have many options.
当然
Of course not.
自从佩德罗·维多利亚到来后 我们从未如此繁荣
And we've never prospered so much since the arrival of Pedro Victoria.
这得感谢俄国人
You should thank the Russians for that.
如果西班牙人还在 情况显然会不一样
Obviously it wouldn't be the same if the Spanish were still here.
你觉得呢 上尉
What do you think, Captain?
没有俄国人我们更好吗
Are we better off with the Russians?
我认为唐·塔迪奥说得对
I think Don Tadeo is right.
尽管没人知道俄国人的想法
Although no one really knows what the Russians think.
-再来点雪莉酒 上尉  -谢谢
More sherry, Captain? - Thanks.
洛丽塔
Lolita?
-什么  -你还好吗
What? - Is everything OK?
还好 抱歉 我只是有点累了
Sure. Yes, sorry. I'm just a bit tired.
你在担心什么
What's worrying you?
你一整晚都心不在焉的
You were distracted almost the whole evening.
我没事 只是
I'm fine, only...
不想让我爱的人发生什么不测
I don't want anything bad to happen to those I love.
我发誓要抓住佐罗 我一定会的
I promised to hunt Zorro down and I will.
我走之前想看看你的笑容
I want a smile before I go.
好好休息
Get some rest.
晚安
Good night.
你要学会礼貌 你对上尉太无礼了
You must learn to behave. You were rude to the captain.
别装了 你想取消我的遗产
Don't pretend, you want to nullify my estate.
你被宠坏了 就是这样
You're spoiled, that's what you are.
你根本不在乎我的幸福
You don't care about my happiness,
只想扩大你的农场
you only care about expanding your ranch.
-洛丽塔 不要  -妈妈 这是真的
Lolita, no. - Mama, it's true.
别胡说 农场跟着没关系
Don't talk nonsense, the ranch has nothing to do with it.
至少有勇气承认
At least have the courage to admit it.
你跟谁这种语气说话
Who do you think you're talking to? l
不管你是不是我父亲 再敢对我动手我就杀了你
Father or not, lay a hand on me again and I'll kill you.
我是认真的
I mean it.
让她走 让她走
Leave her, leave her.
别生她的气
Take no notice of her.
她太激动了
She's very worked up.
她会想通的
She'll get over it.
希望如此
I hope so.
晚餐期间她一直摆弄她的订婚戒指
At dinner she was playing constantly with her engagement ring.
她在犹豫
She's hesitating.
让她自己做决定 别逼她
Let her make her own decisions and don't confront her.
如果你反对婚姻 她执意结婚 你会失去她的
If you oppose the wedding, she'll marry and you'll lose her.
救命
Help.
你是谁
Who are you?
何塞·安东尼奥·拉米雷斯
Jose Antonio Ramirez.
救命
Help.
求你 救我
Help me, please.
拉米雷斯的弟弟
Ramirez's brother.
水 要水
Water, water.
别激动 别激动
Relax, relax.
慢点 慢点喝
Slowly, slowly.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你是怎么逃出来的
How did you manage to escape?
他放了我
He freed me.
佐罗放了我
Zorro freed me.
告诉州长
Tell the Governor.
帮我带他去办公室
Help me take him to the office.
快点
Quickly!
他在路上晕倒了
He passed out on the way.
身体很虚弱
He's very weak.
通知医生 他在酒吧里
Tell the doctor, he'll be in the saloon.
长官
Sir.
蒙纳斯特里奥
Monasterio.
你确定是佐罗放了他的
Are you sure Zorro freed him?
他是这么说的
That's what he said.
我们以后再讨论
We'll discuss this later.
长官
Sir.
罗斯医生呢
Where is Doctor Ros?
他跟一个姑娘刚上楼
He just went upstairs with one of the girls.
4号房间
Room 4.
穿上衣服跟我走
Get dressed, you must come with me.
-现在  -就现在
Now? - Now.
事关生死
It's a matter of life or death.
他已经过世了
There's nothing you can do.
你可以再检查一下
Examine him if you wish.
脉搏停止了
He's dead.
抱歉让你白跑一趟 医生
I'm sorry for making you come for nothing, Doctor.
没关系 要我叫验尸官吗
No, never mind. Shall I call the undertaker?
不用了
No, don't worry.
他怎么死掉的
How did he die?
他突然开始抽搐
He suddenly started convulsing
几秒钟之后就
and a few seconds later...
如果他受伤的话 可能是内出血
It could've been internal bleeding, if he was injured...
如果这里没其他的事
Well, if you don't need me for anything else,
我就去找女人了
the lady is waiting for me.
我还以为你在拉米雷斯牧场遭攻击那天死了
I thought you died at the Ramfrez ranch.
张二爷 不是所有事都能如您所愿
Not everything turns out as one expects.
你言之有理 我不应该拿你当赌注
You're right, I shouldn't have gambled with you.
孔子曰
Confucius says:
错而不改
"The man who makes a mistake and doesn't correct it
是谓过也
makes another mistake".
我现在是迪亚哥·德拉维加的管家
I'm the housekeeper for Diego De la Vega now.
先生派我来这儿买东西
Mr. De la Vega told me to do the shopping
店主也盯着我看 只因为我是中国人
and the store owner watches me like a hawk because I'm Chinese.
想必张老也知道 在洛杉矶是没人相信中国人的
As you know, Mr. Tchang, in Los Angeles no one trusts the Chinese.
你把这个交给迪亚哥先生
You, give this to sefior Diego.
明天我们就把订好的东西送到牧场去
We'll take everything crossed off to the ranch tomorrow.
明白了吗
Understood?
她说剩下的她明天直接送到农场去
She said she'll take the rest to the ranch.
谢谢你
Thank you.
在下祝你好运
Good luck in the next hand.
这场牌局还没结束呢
The game isn't over yet.
直说吧 朋友
Fire away, mon ami.
你知道我父亲和拉米雷斯有生意往来吗
Do you know if my father and Ramirez had business together?
据我所知没有 他们关系融洽
Not that I know of. They had a cordial relationship.
他们的死亡之间可能有联系吗
Could there be a link between their deaths?
官方说他们俩都是被佐罗杀害的
The official version says that Zorro killed both of them.
你想说什么
What are you getting at?
拉米雷斯说我父亲从他那里买了炸药
Ramirez told me my father bought explosives from him.
对 用于苏格兰矿井
For the Scotsman's mine, yes.
不幸的是 你父亲很多生意都失败了
Your father had a lot of business that unfortunately came to nothing.
-你知道他在找什么吗  -当然 跟别人一样
·Do you know what he was after? - Sure. What are they all after?
煤矿
Coal.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
很抱歉让你失望了 朋友
I'm sorry to disappoint you, mon ami.
加利福尼亚没有黄金
There's no gold in California.
真正值钱的是土地
The real gold is land.
希望你不会被我要说的话冒犯到
I hope you're not offended by what I'm about to say.
请讲
Please.
你想象不到我来这里之前都听说了什么
You can't imagine how many things I've been told since I came.
由于州长 农场主越来越富裕
Thanks to the Governor, the ranchers are increasingly richer.
农民和当地人却越来越贫穷
The peasants and natives, poorer.
如果他们失去一切
If they lose everything,
他们就会无所畏惧
they'll also lose fear.
如果他们无所畏惧
And if they lose fear,
就会血流成河
blood will flow.
佐罗杀了拉米雷斯的弟弟
Zorro killed Ramirez's brother.
-什么  -你确定
What? - Are you sure?
验尸官的消息可靠吗
Is the undertaker reliable enough for you?
我们有事情做了 亲爱的 失陪
We have work to do, ma cherie. Excuse me.
他是无辜的
He was innocent.
他跟他哥哥的事没关系
He had nothing to do with his brother.
佐罗对拉米雷斯之死给州长的回应
ZORRO RESPONDS TO GOVERNOR RAMIREZ DIES
我不明白 她根本不在乎佐罗的声誉
I don't get it. She doesn't even care about Zorro's reputation.
我必须做点什么
I must do something.
你是来报仇的吗
Have you come to avenge yourself?
如果是 你早就没命了
If I had, you'd be dead.
查看窗户
Check the windows.
感谢你前来提醒我
It's thoughtful of you to come and tell me.
不是我干的
I didn't do it.
这让他无可否认
It's so there's no doubt about whom they chose.
你来干什么
Why have you come?
我没杀拉米雷斯的弟弟
I didn't kill Ramirez's brother.
我相信了你
I believed you...
你说不能靠复仇 所以我放了他
when you said that revenge was not the way and I freed him.
-半死不活的  -他当时活得好好的
Half dead. - He was alive.
之后的事跟我没关系
What happened after is not up to me.
有人杀了他
Someone killed him.
莫纳斯塔里奥发现了他 他绝不会那么做的
Monasterio found him, he'd never do that.
这是违反规定的
It goes against the rules.
我不知道是谁动的手 反正不是我
I don't know who did it, but it wasn't me.
我相信你
I believe you.
接下来怎么办
What's the next great idea?
我们立下盟约 携手合作
We make a pact and join forces.
干什么
What for?
解救你的人
To liberate your people.
来不及了
There's no time now.
你的应变能力怎么样
How are you at improvisation?
这身衣服对你太大了
The suit is too big for you
对你太大了
It's too big for you.
你确定这样能行
Are you sure this will work?
考虑到你上一个主意
Considering the result of your last idea,
我觉得你应该信我一回
I believe I deserve the benefit of the doubt.
为什么
Why?
你怕又会有炸药
Are you afraid there'll be another explosion?
我可不想还没替我的人复仇就没命了
I don't want to die before I avenge my people.
活下去的好理由
A good reason to live.
准备好
Ready!
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
我还有私事要去拉米雷斯家解决
I have personal matters to settle at the Ramirez house.
什么东西
What was that?
快点 都拿上
Quickly! Get it all!
我看不见他
I can't see him!
快点
Come on!
他在哪儿
Where is he?
有没有可能我父亲参加了什么秘密社团
Is it possible that my father belonged to a secret society?
或者对抗秘密社团
Or was fighting them?
对 杀我父亲的人穿着这个
My father's killers wore them, yes.
-您的早餐  -谢谢 梅
Breakfast. - Thank you, Mei.
尝一尝
Try it.
她要我尝一尝
I'm to try it?
问她这是什么
Ask her what it is.
这是我们中国的早餐
The traditional breakfast of China.
你尝尝这个 这个好吃
Try this delicious food.
太难吃了
It's terrible.
谢谢先生 我就知道您会喜欢
Thank you, sir I knew you'd like it.
给你尝尝
Here, try it.
你尝尝 你也尝尝
Go on, try it.
好吃吧
It's delicious.
那我先下去了
I'm glad you like it.
我这样做对吗
I don't know if I'm doing the right thing.
我戴上面具时叫所有人不要复仇 要寻求正义
I put on the mask and tell everyone to not seek revenge, but justice.
可是取下面具 我却替自己的父亲复仇
When I take it off, I seek it for the death of my father.
这怎么说得过去
Where's the sense in that?
佐罗给于人们希望 对
Zorro gives people hope, yes.
不知道能不能给我希望
I don't know if he'll give it to me.
恐怕我的发现会让我失望
I'm afraid that what I may find will disappoint me.
我 我害怕的不是真想
No, I'm not afraid of the truth.
而是带来的后果
I'm worried about its consequences.
有件事我没告诉你
There's something I haven't told you.
我跟她定了协议
I made a pact with her.
有件事只有我们合作才能做到
There's a matter we can only settle if we act together.
把他们全部救出来等于是自投罗网
Getting them all out of prison is a suicide mission.
我们必须从这里行动
We have to do it here.
在这里 这里 还有这里备好马匹和马车
We'll need horses and wagons here, here and here.
不 我们有炸药
No, we have explosives.
今晚就袭击监狱
We attack the prison tonight.
对 我们顺便炸掉了州长官邸
Yes, and in passing we blow up the Governor's mansion,
这是压迫的象征
it's a symbol of oppression.
我喜欢
I like it.
妈妈桑 来一瓶酒 两个酒杯
Mami, a bottle, two glasses...
一个房间
and a key.
我有话要问你
I must speak to you.
行吧 今天也是刻不容缓吗
Sure, and it can't wait today either.
我帮你留着
I'll keep it for later.
说吧 上尉
Tell me what you want, Captain.
我离开拉米雷斯的弟弟时
When I left Ramirez's brother,
他是有伤 可是并不致命
he was injured but not at death's door.
你在暗示我业务不精
Are you insinuating that I don't know my profession,
还是说他是被谋杀的
or that he was murdered?
我没有任何暗示
I'm not insinuating anything.
只想知道真相
I just want to know the truth.
那就只有一个办法
There's only one way to find out.
去问死者本人
By asking the man himself.
跟我来
Follow me.
洛杉矶就像座鬼城
Los Angeles looks like a ghost town.
人们晚上不敢出来 他们害怕
People don't want to come out at night, they're afraid.
害怕什么 怕佐罗
Afraid of Zorro.
怕佐罗
Of Zorro?
不是 怕的是你和你的手下
No, of you and your men.
上尉 只有有钱人才怕佐罗
Captain. Only the rich are afraid of Zorro.
胡安·德·迪奥斯 帮我把他抬起来 我想看看他的背
Juan de Dios, help me lift him. I want to see his back.
行了 谢谢
That's enough. Thank you.
不管是死是活 他都是个人 放尊重点
Alive or dead, he's still a person. Treat him with respect.
抱歉 上尉
Sorry, Captain.
接下来交给我 谢谢 你可以走了
I'll take care of it. Thank you. Leave us alone.
他去世的那天晚上
No signs of internal bleeding
没有内部出血迹象
on the night of his death.
那他就是自然死亡
Then he died of natural causes.
也不一定
Not necessarily.
唯一确定的是
All we know for sure
他是窒息而死
is that he suffocated.
当有人窒息时
When someone suffocates,
我们通常会击打他们 让他们呼吸
we normally hit them so that they react or breathe.
你看
Look,
我这辈子见过很多这样的击打
I've seen a lot of blows in my life,
而这具尸体没有任何心肺复苏的迹象
and this body shows no attempt at resuscitation.
我可以对天发誓
I'll swear it on the Bible.
这就是我的结论
That is my conclusion.
你可以自行定论
Now you can draw yours.
正义
Justicel
州长 法官在哪儿
Governor, where's the judge?
你们有权寻求公平正义
You ask for justice and you're right.
因为只有公平正义
Because justice and the law
才能维持秩序
ensure order.
可是不是我剥夺了你们的正义
But I'm not the one who took it from you.
是他们
It was them.
佐罗和他的手下 还有这些人
Zorro and his men, these men here,
他们像懦夫一样杀死了拉米雷斯他们
killed Ramirez and his men in a cowardly manner.
袭击农场 偷窃食物
They attacked farms, stole your food
杀害农场主和无辜农民
and killed ranchers and innocent peasants.
何塞·安东尼奥·拉米雷斯被佐罗无情地杀害
Jose Antonio Ramirez was executed by Zorro in cold blood.
你们却要求给他手下公平审判
And you demand a fair trial for his henchmen?
所有法官都会判他们死刑
No judge would sentence them to anything but death!
对洛杉矶 加利福尼亚和墨西哥的所有敌人
And we shall deal death
我们都该处以极刑
to all enemies of Los Angeles, California and Mexico.
天哪 州长官邸
Oh my God! The Governor's house!
怎么回事
What was that?
一切就绪了吗
Is everything ready?
那你知道该怎么做
Then you know what you must do.
给我彻底解决了他
Finish him off once and for all.
-长官  -那些犯人  -你还在等什么
Sir, the prisonersWhat are you waiting for?
炸药在州长的官邸里
The explosion was at the Governor's housel
没人能上绞刑架
No one gets up on the gallows!
保护好广场
Secure the squarel
我们走
Let's go!
上尉
Captain!
是佐罗
It's Zorro! l
快去抓住他
Go up and get him!
听州长的命令 快行动
Do as the Governor saysl Go!
掩护他 快去
Cover himl Gol
他要逃走了
He's getting awayl
杀了他 我要他死
Kill him! I want his head!
上尉 你在干什么
Captain! What are you doing?
有两个佐罗 是诡计 快回来
There were two! It's a trick! Come backl
开火
Firel
你还在等什么 杀了他
What are you waiting for? Kill him!
找到他们 他们不可能跑远
Find them! They can't be farl
我要他们全部都死 听见了吗 全部都死
I want them dead! Do you hear me? Dead!
你怎么能射偏
How could you miss?
他太远了
He was too far away.
你太让我失望了 上尉 太让我失望
You disappoint me, Captain. You disappoint mel
他们都安全了
They're all safe.
你遵守了诺言
You kept your word.
你这是道歉
That is an apology.
这是我们合作的结果
We did this together.
从此以后我们分道扬镳
Now each goes their own way.
今天你看到了还有其他办法可以达到目的
Today you saw that there are other ways to do things.
你想让这世界和平
You want to bring peace to this world.
我想要的是改变
I want to change it.
白人永远不会理解神圣的力量
The white man will never understand the energy of the sacred.
你也不懂
And you won't
因为你连自己来自哪里都不清楚
because you don't even know the land where you were born.
你信守了承诺 值得我尊敬 别让我失望
You keep your word and that deserves my respect. Don't lose it.
为何我们不能继续合作
Why not work together?
因为佐罗只有一个
Because there's only one Zorro.
你愿意屈居第二吗
Would you agree to be my second?
我也不愿意
Neither would I.
OCR@China_sky
欢迎加入OCR小组 QQ群：906722936 字幕优先发布于群内